[JUNE] Why didn't you tell me?
Your father never treated you
as if you're adopted, did he?
Who's my real father?
He's gone.
He never came back.
He could be dead already.
That's why ever since then,
your father raised you
as his own.
You know, sweetie,
if he were still alive,
he wil fight for your rights
personally himself.
Because he's still a part
of Don Nato's family.
No matter how distant.
But Ima, it's about
my personality.
I wish you had given me
a choice.
Now I look like a liar
and a fool.
My dear, you are not a liar.
I am.
[IMA] I was the one who kept
the truth from them.
[IMA SNIFFLES]
It just really pains me
to see you suffer
just to keep us alive. [CRYING]
That's why when I saw Attorney,
I thought...
that this is your chance
for you to live a life
that I'll never be able
to provide.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
[SOBS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[PING] If only I could take
all your pain away, June.
But I think now's not the time.
[SOBS]
Papa Ping?
[JUNE SOBBING]
Papa Ping?!
Ima, why didn't he go in?
Only he could answer that.
Ima, what if... [SNIFFLES]
what if he believes
that I'm a scammer?
What if he doesn't trust me
anymore?
Ima, he's already been through
a lot.
[SOBS] Ima...
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]